Here we go, Wildstock, Asadaido, Scandal Tamomi.
Pleased to meet you.
Here we are today.
D'oh!
It's amazing!
It's so loud!
Why am I speaking in one language?
This is the venue for Tokyo Island, which will be held on the 10th and 11th of June.
We filmed here once last September.
We did, didn't we?
It was a beautiful day.
The blackest clouds I've ever seen.
They came from far away.
A clear band.
It's stopping.
That's great.
It was the blackest cloud you've ever seen in a movie.
I thought it was CG.
You can see the video of this event in the past.
This time, I am the organizer of the event.
Mr. Kano, the organizer of the event.
Mr. Kano, the organizer of the event
Yes, sir.
Please come in.
Hello.
Pleased to meet you.
Hello. - Hello.
It's been a while.
It's been eight months.
Yes, it has.
Eight months.
Clear skies!
Thank goodness.
Looks like it's going to be okay today.
There's nowhere to go.
Clouds.
There's no clouds anywhere.
Good, good, good.
You know, that was actually a sign from last year's Tokyo Ariando.
The notice...
It was a completely honest warning.
I heard you had a lot of trouble.
We at the headquarters are looking at the screen together with the weather forecaster.
with the weather forecaster.
Something amazing is coming from Shizuoka!
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming!
It looked like Godzilla or something was coming.
We kept watching the rain clouds.
On the second day, it fell.
It was very close.
I see.
We'll talk more about that later.
Where was the stage?
Last year, the stage was that way.
That way.
And the workshops over here.
There's a lot of dinosaurs here.
You said dinosaurs.
There were a lot of dinosaurs.
They're here this year, too.
They're here?
Yes, they are.
They were saying there would be a lot of dinosaurs.
But this is still an uninhabited island.
No one can enter without a machine like this.
The reason for this is that we are making this kind of thing right now.
We are going to hold a festival in the middle of construction.
We have to coexist with the construction workers.
This time, the construction workers are working hard on that side.
They're working on that side.
As a result, we're going to have the stage on this side.
This side is mainly for music.
And on the other side, we'll have workshops and a dock run.
There's also a dock run.
We're going to have camping and a lot of other things to do.
and many other things to do.
It's a music festival.
That's right.
Last year was really tough for me, you know, emotionally.
I've always felt that the people who shared that with me last year are my relatives.
It all started from the stage of the oracle.
I'm sorry, but I've decided that you two are relatives of Tokyo Announcers.
I'm sorry, but as a result of setting you two up as members of the Tokyo Announcers, you will be appearing as the Takiokai again.
And finally, you're going to appear on Scandal.
Thank you very much.
I'm very happy.
What about the last Scandal? There was an awkward moment.
There was an awkward moment for all of us.
What do you mean your name's not on the list?
Well, we were the first to offer it to you.
So, with the help of my family.
I'd like to make this a great success.
I'll tell you all about it.
We've set up tents and tarps over there.
I'd like to hear more about it there.
If you keep listening to me like this, I'm going to talk all the time.
You talk too much.
That's not true.
You're going to start talking here?
That's not the point.That's not the point.
You talk a little bit away from me.
Here's the thing.
You're still talking.
This is where the cross-country horses ran in the Tokyo Olympics.
Horses.
Congratulations on the second Tokyo Island!
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad.
After the first one, it was your first time.
How was the response?
You did it in a place where no one had ever set foot before.
That's right.
You know, the first customers came here.
First, they took a bus to the bottom of the park.
Then, when they entered the park...
They have to go through a steel plate about 2 meters under construction.
Are you sure about this entrance?
It has the atmosphere of a place you're not supposed to enter.
I had no idea where to enter.
I had no idea!
When we went inside, we found this huge place, the size of Tokyo Dome.
The weather was bad, but it was such a great place in Tokyo.
I had never experienced a place like this in Tokyo where you can do all kinds of things and play.
I don't think I've ever experienced anything like this before.
I think it's just so much potential.
I want to complain about the weather and all that, but
But I remember clapping them on the shoulder and saying how much fun it was.
I remember people clapping me on the shoulder and saying they had a great time.
The best thing is that it's easy to get to because it's not a big city.
That's right.
You have to come to see us to understand.
But those who come can understand.
I want to say again and again that accessibility is the best.
There are a lot of festivals.
But if you go far away from the festival, it's a little bit difficult to get there.
That's true.
That's why...
As I mentioned earlier...
Last time...
Tomo-chan said something...
No scandals? Yes.
Yes...
What a scandal!
Is she here today?
Yes, she is.
I've invited all our members.
Well, let's invite her in.
Come in, Scandal.
Go ahead.
Please, come in.
Please.
Jessie.
Please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please
Please have a seat.
Please.
I'm a little nervous.
It's nice to meet you.
Thank you for the flowers you sent me for the Tokyo show.
Thank you very much.
I wanted to go, but I couldn't.
There are plenty of opportunities for you.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'd love to go.
Flowers.
Yes, flowers.
Not just flowers.
Mr. MIKURA himself.
Great.
Introduce yourself.
Okay.
Please do.
I'm Haruna, the vocalist.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Norina, the drummer.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Mami, the guitarist. Nice to meet you.
Have we met before, Mr. Kano?
I invited you to my debut event.
I invited you to an event when I made my debut, and it's been a little while since then.
Not a little. I've been free for 10 years.
I was your neighbor.
Well, I don't know many people anymore.
You mean you've forgotten Scandara's songs since then?
Is that a terrible thing to say? That's a terrible thing to say.
I am a journalist, you know. I'm a journalist, after all.
I know I look like a nice guy, but...
But as a journalist, what Scandara has done is a very big part of J-Pop and J-Rock.
J-pop and J-rock is a very big thing, and I'd like to talk about it for a minute and a half.
Can I talk for a minute and a half?
One minute.
Please talk.
Nowadays, in this kind of era
The Internet, real life, gender, and generation are all becoming borderless.The internet, real life, gender and generation are all becoming borderless.
Music is being listened to more freely in this country
but it's not like it's all of a sudden.
It didn't happen all of a sudden.
The internet didn't cause it.
It's the music and the artists that have created the path.
It took 10 years for music and artists to create the path to where we are today.
When Scandara came out
When Scandara came out, it was a girl band.
There is a common positioning of a girl band as a girl band.
And they probably went through a lot of hardships.
But you have been trying to stand your ground and make it through.
The place to deliver the power of communication is a live house
TV
Tie-ups
There are various places
We have done all kinds of things.
I think we have reaped the benefits of all of them.
Bands that have seen the backs of those who have done that
In fact, there are so many bands in this country right now
Including all of those people.
In this 2020s
In this borderless era
Solo, pop, rock, band, etc.
And people who are taking root in Japan.
I think I'm one of the pioneers and a very important icon.
I think I am one of the most important icons of the pioneers.
I'm glad.
You say surprisingly good things.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
I've already finished my work.
I'm just getting started.
Thank you.
How do you feel?
I haven't seen you in a really long time.
I thought you didn't really care about me.
I honestly thought you didn't care about me.
I'm glad to know that you've been paying attention to our 17-year history since we formed.
I'm glad that you were able to see our 17 years of history since we formed.
I want to make up the time from here.
That's why I'm really glad that we've continued to do this.
I'm so happy.
If we hadn't continued...
I wouldn't have been invited by Mr. Kano again.
It's not just Mr. Kano.
It's because we've kept going that people understand us.
I'm really glad that the four of us have continued to do this.
I've heard a little bit about you.
I heard that you are challenging yourself.
That's right.
I'm working on a Guinness World Record attempt this summer.
We're working on it.
What kind of record would that be?
The longest active girls' band.
No member changes
No hiatuses.
We're on the verge of getting it.
How many years has it been?
17 years since we went on hiatus.
Long time.
17 years in summer.
Has any girl band lasted that long?
I don't think so.
I don't know yet.
I guess...
The fact that we don't change members
That's the point.
Bands that have been around for a long time all over the world...
The longevity of a band's survival
is getting longer and longer as time goes by
especially in this country.
But there are some things that have changed left and right.
I think that bands with unique personalities are the ones that succeed.
are the ones who are successful.
And that's the way it goes.
Everyone has their own view of life
And they bump into each other
And then they're in and out.
I mean, there are things like that.
But without that...
17 years without it is really amazing.
I think people who are also in bands
I think people who are also in a band feel this most strongly.
Even if we are just normal friends
Even if you're just normal friends, you have your own family problems.
It's a little bit like that, isn't it?
In a band that works closely with each other
Do you have any tips to keep it going?
Do you have any tips?
How do you keep it going for so long?
But I really think about it often.
As you said before...
As you said before.
We all have different personalities.
We're all different ages.
And we are all different in many ways.
But that's the part of us
That's one of the things I respect about you.
We like each other as people.
I see.I see.
You want to make something with these people.
I want to make a creative life with these people.
I've always wanted to make something with these people
I think that's a big part of it.
I think the best thing about being in a band
I think the most important thing for a band
I think the chemistry between the band members is the most important thing.
I think the chemistry between us is the most important part of a band.
I think that's why we've been doing so well
That's the biggest reason why we've been doing so well.
I think that's the biggest thing.
But the other thing is...
I think we can do a little bit better.
There's always been an expectation in the band Scandal
ourselves.
Oh, wow.
I feel like we've already done it.
And dreams that have already come true
We've done a lot of things
That's why I think we can do more
This music
I think this music can be conveyed to many more people
I believe that we can do more
We believe in ourselves
and that we are excited about it.
I think that's a big part of it.
When three or four people get together like this
Because we are together on a regular basis
It's hard to talk about the core of what we're talking about.
There are things that are difficult to talk about, aren't there?
Do you take the opportunity to talk about those things?
There are times when we do.
I think of Scandal as a band.
as a band, apart from ourselves.
I mean, we take care of the band Scandal
We can't let this group die.
It would be a waste.
It's a waste.
It's kind of my life.
I feel that it would be a shame to lose this group in the music industry.
I feel it would be a waste to lose this group in the music industry.
That's why I'm willing to do my best.
I feel like the band should set an example of how to balance all these things.
I feel that all bands should follow your example.
It's a good example for the band to follow, isn't it?
Scandal is a kind of ambition.
I think we're starting to feel the weight of the scandal in a good way.
I guess it's been about 10 years.
I don't know.
But it was big when you started the label.
It's been the last five years or so.
We're doing things on our own.
We're doing more and more of everything.
And then there's the Corona disaster.
And then there's the Corona Disaster, and then there's the personalities.
I've come to value their personalities
I've come to value more and more
I feel like I'm able to value my scandalous self more and more
I've been able to cherish my scandalous self more and more.
About five years ago...
I've been thinking about it for about five years now. I've been joking about it for about five years.
I've been joking about it.
We've been saying that for 5 years.
I've been saying that for five years. People around here are like...
It's been going on for this long.
We were joking about it.
I might actually be able to get it.
And then I realized the gravity of the situation.
I realized the gravity of the situation.
I've come to think that it's really important.
Once again
Mr. Hayazawa
You know...
I'm one of those "A", "B", "C", or "D" approvers.
This time...
The Guinness case.
What do you mean?
You apply to Guinness.
For Guinness' sake.
I'm not sure if that's what they're saying.
Specifically.
Apparently, there hasn't been a change of members.
I can see that on the internet.
But in those 17 years...
I wonder if they've been active for 17 years.
Or did they take a break during that period? Something like that.
That's the kind of thing
I have to do research.
We're probably asking a lot of people for their approval.
I'm probably asking a lot of people.
I'm one of them.
Why do you think it's so important?
You know...
I heard it.
Listen.
Are you sure you want me to do it?
I asked.
If you look too hard...If you look at it too much
I'll have everything.
I see.
That's why someone with such an objective stance
is the most credible.
It was something like that.
I'm thankful for that.
I'm grateful for the opportunity I was given last year.
I was able to do it.
You know...
I spent a lot of time
I wrote a lot of things.
Thank you very much.
That's what I'm trying to say.
That's exactly what I meant.
I worked with him when he was making his debut.
That's one of the things that convinced me.
I'd like to talk about how this band has been performing over the years.
I'd like to know how this band has been performing over the years.
I'm going to testify about how the band has been performing over the years
I'm going to testify in various ways.
So if I get off on this
I'll have to go through
I'll have to go through all the research
I'll be certified by the Guinness Book of Records.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I'm not sure about this again.
I'm challenging myself.
I hope to be certified.
If I get certified, I want to have a party with everyone.
But if you get certified...
I'll be busy again.
I wonder...
I think I'll do it.
What do you want to do next?
You're going to talk about what you want to do next?
Of course.
It's important.
But now...
What do you want to do now?
I want to be on stage.
I want to be in a place like this...
To be honest, I don't really want to.
But we've come this far.
We've been working so hard as a four-piece.
I want to make it last as long as possible.
As long as we can.
As long as we can
We can do our music happily
We'll find a way to do it
to find a way to do it in a way that makes us happy.
That's the healthiest thing I've ever heard.
The scandal is that
June 10th.
I'll be on the show.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
If I say too much, it's gonna rain.
I mean, it's a very convenient location.
But there's no such thing as neighborhoods.
A deserted island?
So there's no volume limit.
We'd like you to put out a big bouquet of music.
We'd all like to be bathed in it.
Scandal.
I'd love to bask in it.
I think it's already been announced.
I'm sure it's already been announced, but it's going to happen very quickly.
I'm going to be in it.
I'm Asuwa.
I'm a camper.
I'm going to be on stage
I'm looking forward to that too.
Seriously, I don't know what we're going to do.
I think it's going to be a talk.
Maybe a talk, I don't know.
I'm just getting ready to go on stage.
I'm getting ready to light a fire.
That's great.
We've got it all set up.
It's not easy to do at an event.
It'll be fine.
It's like making a fire from flint.
I want to see. I want to see.
It's so detailed, I don't think anyone can see it.
You need a monitor.
It's a tiny flower.
Tokyo Island is like that...
There's so much more to Tokyo Island.
Camping with music, of course!
Sauna by the fire
Fireworks.
And of course, delicious gourmet food.And of course, there's the delicious gourmet food.
Dinosaur Expedition
I don't know what this means.
There are a lot of dinosaurs!
Pet Land
Petland is like a dockland?
Yes, it is.
We enclose the animals in an enclosure.
You can play inside.
So you already have a pet?
So I can bring my pet?
Only in Petland.
You can't have your dog or pets only in Petland.
It's not that you can only stay with your pets.
while being with your pet.
You can see the live performance.
so that you can enjoy the show with your pets.
Haruna has a dog.
That's right.
It's really me and my dog.
It's a miniature dachshund.
Maybe I should bring him along.
No... no... no...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't be so chill.
Oh, yeah.
The sauna.
We've got one of those big tents.
We have one big tent that can hold about 30 people.
In there.
Charismatic Heatwave City
A lot of people come.
Some of them are musicians.
Natsunami market
They were there last time there was a big storm.
The musician from Androp.
Maybe they'll be there.
They're calling it the Music Sauna.
So we can get heatwaves.
I'm all for it.
Heat waves to music at the moment.
I see.
Bang!
I'm thinking of setting the fireworks to music too.
I'm so excited!
And what's with the dinosaurs?
I'm really curious about this.
Dinosaurs are all the rage.
Dinosaurs.
We're going to put some dinosaurs.
We're putting some dinosaurs there.
Dinosaur shop with a car.
An electric car.
And we'll be guiding the dinosaurs
We're going to guide you through the dinosaurs.
We're going to meet a lot of dinosaurs.
The dinosaurs will be there to greet you
the dinosaurs will pick you up.
It's like a safari park.
And recently, in the U.S.
Tyrannosaurus Race in the U.S.
Tyrannosaurus race in the U.S.!
You know, the stuffed ones.
I did that at a festival during Golden Week this year.
I did it at a festival during Golden Week this year and it was very popular!
I did it at a festival in the spring.
It was a big hit at the spring festival.
You're going to race?
That's fun!
I don't know if I can do this.
I'm a Tyrannosaurus.
It's Japanese, so culturally...
I'm wondering if we could have a Tyrannosaurus Sumo.
I'm wondering if we can have a Tyrannosaurus Sumo.
I see... I see...
Sounds like a lot of fun.
Dinosaurs and Tyrannos.
I'm really excited about it.
So many activities to do.
And what kind of food will there be?
There's going to be a lot of food at the festival.
There will be a lot of different kinds of food at the festival.
And there's also a meat forest.
There's also a meat forest.
To put it simply.
A barbecue tent or a plaza.
In a place like that
Everyone can eat as much meat as they want in this limited time.
All-you-can-eat meat!
Of course, domestic beef!
We brought in some delicious beef from Kyushu.
We're going to do this.
When we were talking about doing this...
Mr. Wild or something
I got a call from me.
We
I've been trying to get in touch with you.
I said, "Wait a minute.I said, wait a minute.
He said it's not just about the meat.
When you cook meat in a place like this.
What's the most important thing?
Sauce.
He said, "Sauce.
And that's when the Wild Stocks came in.
And then Wild Stocks came in.
I'm in a lot of pain right now.
I'm being held down a lot right now.
This is the one.
The package is still stylish!
It's been redesigned.
It's better than when I saw it.
The label is better.
It's prettier.
It's just the two of us.
Mixing spices.
I think this would be good in it.
We'll start with a concept.
You like it, don't you?
Do you guys know about this?
I heard you talking about making it.
I'd like you to try it.
I'm curious.
I'd like to eat it.
They bring their own meat and stuff.
We'd like you to put it in this.
They sell this kind of seasoned stuff.
They sell the ones with the meat in them, but...
But we don't sell packets of sauce only.
You can put whatever meat you like in it.
and grill it, it's the best!
Have you ever tried it, Mr. Hikano?
I'm sorry, I'm just setting this up.
I wasn't sure if I was allowed to say I've eaten it.
I didn't know if I could say I'd eaten it, so I've been trying to hide it.
I did eat it.
How was it?
And it's delicious.
It leaves little bits in your mouth.
The mustard is so good.
I'm so happy.
It was so good!
The fact that it's not even grainy.
The aftertaste is the mustard.
It's like a double treat, isn't it?
That's right.
The key is that it comes in packs.
Campers want to keep their luggage as small and light as possible.
They want to keep their luggage as small and light as possible.
Bottles are too heavy.
They are bulky, so we made them flat.
And it's easy to dispose of.
You're going to put meat in here, right?
That's right.
And your hands don't get dirty.
This is what we're selling.
We're selling it at a store in Tokyo.
The moment it goes on sale
It's sold out right away.
It's already a big hit.
It's a festival meal.
Rice burger with wild pack
Rice burgers.
We developed it last time.
It's really good.
I just heard that you're going to this festival.
You're going to our festival?
I'd love to go.
Can you go?
To be honest, it's really good.
I'd like you to put it on.
I'm going to go with Scandal.
I'd like to ask you three in particular
I have a question.
Can I ask you one question?
The world of food...
It's an evil path.
I'm getting ahead of myself.
When I get in here...
Tomomi, you're going to be better than you've ever been.
You're going to become more powerful than ever.
I see.
And I'll be honored to be a part of it.
I'm honored to be honored at the festival.
I've been a huge part of it.
As a music journalist.
I'd like to ask the band members
I'd like to ask the band members what they think
I asked them what they thought about it.
It was a very serious conversation.
That's how serious we were getting.
I hope you'll try it.
I'd like you to judge after you try it.
Let's do that.
It's a rice burger that you can hold in your hand so that you can eat it easily at the festival.
It's a rice burger that you can hold in your hand for easy eating at festivals!
I'll tell you what.
Years from now.
I don't mind talking about what we should do at convenience stores.I'm not afraid to start talking about what to do at the convenience store.
I hope it starts.
I'm a little worried
I'm worried that we'll lose the name.
I'm afraid that we'll lose the name and it'll be "Tomominon" or something like that.
I'm scared.
Anyway...
Let's all try it together.
Yay!
That's it! Let's grill it!
Here are the rice burgers!
Congratulations!
Please eat it!
Bon appétit!
One serving.
Delicious!
You have rice.
Delicious.
Oh, my God.